(
"ai_sub_version": "2.9.1",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 7,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 15,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.1-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600,
"overwrite_system_prompt": false
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch"
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"run": 5,
"max": 5,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false
)
Attention For Visitors
Please be aware of flashing lights during the performance. Cheering loudly is ok.
hololive 7th fes. Ridin' on Dreams
PENLIGHT COLORS
ねえ、君がいたからだよ
Hey, it's because you were there
ねえ、ありがとうを何度も
Hey, saying thanks again and again
今すぐに伝えたいんだ
I want to tell you right now
さあ乗り込もう！
Come on, let's jump on!
Ridin' on dreams
Yeah!!
Wow oh oh...
Hey!! (Hey!!) Hey!! (Hey!!)
Yeah!!
あぁ小さな夢から
Ah, from a small dream
想像できないような
To feelings that I couldn't even imagine
想いになったんだ
These feelings have grown...
わくわく止まらない！
My excitement won't stop!
何度迷ったって僕ら
No matter how many times we get lost
絆が舵になる
Our bond becomes the rudder
ちょっとの不安だってさ
Even a little anxiety
吹き飛ばせちゃうんだよ
We can blow it away
果てない旅路を今
We are rowing on an endless journey now
漕いでる途中に困難もあるでしょう
There must be difficulties on the way
それも力に変えて
Turn even those into strength
一緒に進むんだよ！
And move forward together!
ねえ、君がいたからだよ
Hey, it's because you were there
ねえ、夢では終われない
Hey, we can't end with just a dream
荒波も乗り越えていこう
Let's overcome the rough waves too
“らしく”輝いていたい
I want to keep shining "like us"
ねえ、君と会えたことが
Hey, the fact that I could meet you
ねえ、宝物だから
Hey, is a treasure
手を取り合い声かけ合って
Taking each other's hands, calling out to each other
地図など無い未知の世界で
In a world of the unknown with no map
まだまだ行こう！
Let's keep going!
Ridin' on dreams
Wow oh oh...
Hey!! (Hey!!) Hey!! (Hey!!)
Yeah!!
急な風が僕らの
Even if sudden winds
行く先乱そうとも
Disturb our path
あの日誓ったんだ
We swore it that day
覚悟は揺るがない
Our determination won't waver
ちゃんとしなきゃ！って背中
The push to "You have to do it properly!"
明日への橋になる
Becomes a bridge to tomorrow
もっと大事にしなきゃね
We have to cherish it more
“あたりまえ”は無いから
Because there is nothing that's "taken for granted"
小さな船から始まるストーリー
A story starting from a small boat
どっから始めたらいいかもがいて
Struggling wondering where to start
少しずつね輪になって見つけた
Little by little, becoming a circle, we found it
何にも代えられない夢だ
It's a dream that cannot be replaced by anything
Wow oh oh oh oh oh
未完成も愛して
Love the incompleteness too
Wow oh oh oh oh oh
想いは一つだ
Our feelings are one
Wow oh oh oh oh oh
僅かな希望でも
Even if it's just a little hope
僕と君でずっと
With you and me forever
馬鹿にされても
Even if we're made fun of
信じたい！
I want to believe!
ねえ、ありがとうじゃ足りない
Hey, "thank you" is not enough
ねえ、想いが溢れちゃうんだよ
Hey, my feelings are overflowing
ずっと一緒だよ！
We'll be together forever!
ねえ、君がいたからだよ
Hey, it's because you were there
ねえ、夢では終われない
Hey, we can't end with just a dream
荒波も乗り越えていこう
Let's overcome the rough waves too
“らしく”輝いていたい
I want to keep shining "like us"
ねえ、君と会えたことが
Hey, the fact that I could meet you
ねえ、宝物だから
Hey, is a treasure
手を取り合い声かけ合って
Taking each other's hands, calling out to each other
地図など無い未知の世界で
In a world of the unknown with no map
まだまだ行けるから！
Because we can still keep going!
ひとりじゃない
We are not alone
何度でも立ち上がってさ
Stand up again and again
笑い合っていたい
I want to keep laughing together
願いだってみんなで、さあ！
Even our wishes, everyone together, come on!
手を繋いで想像も超えて
Holding hands, surpassing even imagination
まだまだ行こう！
Let's keep going!
Ridin' on dreams
Wow oh oh...
ねえ、君がいたからだよ
Hey, it's because you were there
ねえ、ありがとうを何度も
Hey, saying thanks again and again
今すぐに伝えたいんだ
I want to tell you right now
さあ乗り込もう！
Come on, let's jump on!
Ridin' on dreams
Yeah!!
Wow oh oh...
Hey!! (Hey!!) Hey!! (Hey!!)
Yeah!!
あぁ小さな夢から
Ah, from a small dream
想像できないような
To feelings that I couldn't even imagine
想いになったんだ
These feelings have grown...
わくわく止まらない！
My excitement won't stop!
何度迷ったって僕ら
No matter how many times we get lost
絆が舵になる
Our bond becomes the rudder
ちょっとの不安だってさ
Even a little anxiety
吹き飛ばせちゃうんだよ
We can blow it away
果てない旅路を今
We are rowing on an endless journey now
漕いでる途中に困難もあるでしょう
There must be difficulties on the way...
あぁ小さな夢から
Ah, from a small dream...
想像できないような
...it became a feeling...
想いになったんだ
...I couldn't have imagined.
わくわく止まらない!
The excitement won't stop!
何度迷ったって僕ら
No matter how many times we get lost,
絆が舵になる
our bonds become the rudder.
ちょっとの不安だってさ
Even a little bit of anxiety...
吹き飛ばせちゃうんだよ
...can be blown away.
果てない旅路を今
We're in the middle of rowing...
漕いでる途中に困難もあるでしょう
...through the endless journey, where there must be difficulties, too.
それも力に変えて
Let's turn those into strength, too...
一緒に進むんだよ!
...and go forward together!
ねえ、君がいたからだよ
Hey, it's because you were there.
ねえ、夢では終われない
Hey, we can't let it end as a dream.
荒波も乗り越えていこう
Let's overcome the rough seas.
らしく輝いていたい
I want to keep on shining in our own way.
ねえ、君と会えたことが
Hey, the fact that I could meet you...
ねえ、宝物だから
...is a treasure,
手を取り合い声かけ合って
so we hold hands, calling out to each other...
地図など無い未知の世界で
...in this unknown world without maps.
まだまだ行こう!
Let's keep going!
Ridin' on dreams
Wow oh oh...
Hey!!(Hey!!) Hey!!(Hey!!)
Hey! (Hey!) Hey! (Hey!)
Yeah!!
急な風が僕らの
Even if sudden winds...
行く先乱そうとも
...try to disrupt where we go,
あの日誓ったんだ
I swore it that day:
覚悟は揺るがない
my determination will not waver.
ちゃんとしなきゃ!って背中
"I have to do it properly!"...
明日への橋になる
...becomes the bridge to tomorrow.
もっと大事にしなきゃね
We have to cherish it more,
“あたりまえ”は無いから
because there's no such thing as "normal."
小さな船から始まるストーリー
A story that starts from a small boat.
どっから始めたらいいかもがいて
Struggling with where to start...
少しずつね輪になって見つけた
...little by little, I found it when we became a circle.
何にも代えられない夢だ
It's a dream that cannot be replaced by anything.
Wow oh oh oh oh oh
未完成も愛して
Love even the incomplete.
Wow oh oh oh oh oh
想いは一つだ
Our feelings are one.
Wow oh oh oh oh oh
僅かな希望でも
Even with a slight hope,
僕と君でずっと
with you and me, forever...
馬鹿にされても
...even if they make fun of us,
信じたい!
I want to believe!
ねえ、ありがとうじゃ足りない
Hey, "thank you" isn't enough.
ねえ、想いが溢れちゃうんだよ
Hey, my feelings are overflowing,
ずっと一緒だよ!
we'll be together forever!
ねえ、君がいたからだよ
Hey, it's because you were there.
ねえ、夢では終われない
Hey, we can't let it end as a dream.
荒波も乗り越えていこう
Let's overcome the rough seas.
らしく輝いていたい
I want to keep on shining in our own way.
ねえ、君と会えたことが
Hey, the fact that I could meet you...
ねえ、宝物だから
...is a treasure,
手を取り合い声かけ合って
so we hold hands, calling out to each other...
地図など無い未知の世界で
...in this unknown world without maps.
まだまだ行けるから!
I know we can still keep going!
ひとりじゃない
We are not alone.
何度でも立ち上がってさ
We'll stand up again and again...
笑い合っていたい
...and keep laughing together.
願いだってみんなで、さあ!
Let's make this wish happen together, come on!
手を繋いで想像も超えて
Hold hands and go beyond our imagination,
まだまだ行こう! Ridin' on dreams
let's keep going! Ridin' on dreams!
ローソンにお越しの皆さん！こんにちはー！
Everyone visiting Lawson! Hello!
2026年3月、ローソンキャンペーン実施決定！
In March 2026, a Lawson campaign is officially confirmed!
今回はこの6人が登場！
This time, these six members will appear!
詳細は3月9日月曜日公開予定！
Details will be revealed on Monday, March 9th!
お楽しみに！
Look forward to it!
ホロライブ SUPER EXPO 2026 Bandai Namcoブースが登場！
The Bandai Namco booth is coming to hololive SUPER EXPO 2026!
注目の最新商品を一挙公開！
Unveiling the highly anticipated latest products!
オリジナルフレームで撮影、会場限定スペシャルフォトブース！
Shoot with original frames! Venue-exclusive special photo booth!
ブースで限定カードがもらえる！
Get a limited card at the booth!
新新規プロジェクトも公開！
And a brand new project will be revealed!
お楽しみに！
Look forward to it!
みるハコ by JOYSOUND!
Miruhaco by JOYSOUND!
hololive 5th fes. Capture the Moment
hololive 6th fes. Color Rise Harmony
and hololive 6th fes. Color Rise Harmony...
今年も配信決定！
...will be streamed this year as well!
Ridin' on Dreams JOYSOUND みるハコで配信決定!!
Ridin' on Dreams is coming to JOYSOUND Miruhako!!
あぁ小さな夢から
Ah, from a small dream...
想像できないような
...it became a feeling...
想いになったんだ
...I couldn't have imagined.
わくわく止まらない！
The excitement won't stop!
何度迷ったって僕ら
No matter how many times we get lost,
絆が舵になる
our bond becomes the rudder.
ちょっとの不安だってさ
We can just blow away...
吹き飛ばせちゃうんだよ
...even a little bit of anxiety.
果てない旅路を今
Right now, we're rowing through...
漕いでる途中に困難もあるでしょう
...an endless journey, where difficulties will also occur.
それも力に変えて
But let's turn that into strength...
一緒に進むんだよ！
...and move forward together!
ねえ、君がいたからだよ
Hey, it's because you were there.
ねえ、夢では終われない
Hey, we can't end it just as a dream.
荒波も乗り越えていこう
Let's overcome the rough waves too.
“らしく”輝いていたい
I want to shine in my own way.
ねえ、君と会えたことが
Hey, the fact that I could meet you...
ねえ、宝物だから
...hey, is a treasure.
手を取り合い声かけ合って
Let's hold hands, call out to each other...
地図など無い未知の世界で
...in a world of the unknown with no map.
まだまだ行こう！
Let's keep going!
ridin' on dreams
wow oh oh…
Wow oh oh...
hey!! (hey!!) hey!! (hey!!)
Hey!! (Hey!!) Hey!! (Hey!!),,og:
yeah!!
急な風が僕らの行く先乱そうとも
Even if a sudden wind disturbs our path ahead,
あの日誓ったんだ
we vowed that day...
覚悟は揺るがない
...our resolve won't waver.
ちゃんとしなきゃ！って背中
The back that says 'I have to do it properly'...
明日への橋になる
...becomes a bridge to tomorrow.
もっと大事にしなきゃね
We have to cherish it more,
“あたりまえ”は無いから
because there's no such thing as 'obvious'.
小さな船から始まるストーリー
A story starting from a small boat...
どっから始めたらいいかもがいて
...struggling, not knowing where to start.
少しずつね輪になって見つけた
Little by little, we formed a circle and found...
何にも代えられない夢だ
...a dream that cannot be replaced by anything.
wow oh oh oh oh oh
未完成も愛して
...love the incompleteness too.
wow oh oh oh oh oh
想いは一つだ
...our feelings are one.
wow oh oh oh oh oh
僅かな希望でも
...even with a slight hope...
僕と君でずっと
...together with you, forever...
馬鹿にされても信じたい！
...even if we're mocked, I want to believe!
ねえ、ありがとうじゃ足りない
Hey, a thank you isn't enough.
ねえ、想いが溢れちゃうんだよ
Hey, my feelings are overflowing.
ずっと一緒だよ！
We're together forever!
ねえ、君がいたからだよ
Hey, it's because you were there.
ねえ、夢では終われない
Hey, we can't end it just as a dream.
荒波も乗り越えていこう
Let's overcome the rough waves too.
“らしく”輝いていたい
I want to shine in my own way.
ねえ、君と会えたことが
Hey, the fact that I could meet you...
ねえ、宝物だから
...hey, is a treasure.
手を取り合い声かけ合って
Let's hold hands, call out to each other...
地図など無い未知の世界で
...in a world of the unknown with no map,
まだまだ行けるから！
because we can still go on!
ひとりじゃない
We're not alone.
何度でも立ち上がってさ
Let's stand up again and again...
笑い合っていたい
...I want to be laughing together.
願いだってみんなで、さあ！
With everyone, the wish too, come on!
手を繋いで想像も超えて
Let's hold hands, exceeding even our imagination...
まだまだ行こう！
...let's keep going!
ridin' on dreams
wow oh oh…
Wow oh oh...
hey!! (hey!!) hey!! (hey!!)
Hey!! (Hey!!) Hey!! (Hey!!),,og:
yeah!!
公演開始までしばらくお待ちください
Please wait a moment until the performance begins.
ご来場のお客様へ：演出の都合上、照明の点滅にご注意ください。声出し応援OKです。
To our visitors: Please be aware of flashing lights during the performance. Cheering loudly is OK.
事前登録受付中！
Pre-registration now open!
ねえ、君がいたからだよ
Hey, it's because you were there.
ねえ、ありがとうを何度も
Hey, I want to say "thank you" over and over again.
今すぐに伝えたいんだ
I want to tell you right now.
さあ乗り込もう！
Come on, let's climb aboard!
ridin' on dreams
yeah！！
Yeah!
wow oh oh…
Wow oh oh...
hey！！(hey！！) hey！！(hey！！)
Hey! (Hey!) Hey! (Hey!)
yeah！！
Yeah!
あぁ小さな夢から
Ah, from a tiny dream...
想像できないような
...into feelings so immense...
想いになったんだ
...that I could never have imagined.
わくわく止まらない！
My excitement just won't stop!
何度迷ったって僕ら
No matter how many times we get lost...
絆が舵になる
...our bond will be our rudder.
ちょっとの不安だってさ
Even a little bit of anxiety...
吹き飛ばせちゃうんだよ
...can be blown away.
果てない旅路を今
On this endless journey now...
漕いでる途中に困難もあるでしょう
...there will surely be hardships along the way.
それも力に変えて
But let's turn even those into strength...
一緒に進むんだよ！
...and move forward together!
ねえ、君がいたからだよ
Hey, it's because you were there.
ねえ、夢では終われぬ
Hey, we can't let this end as just a dream.
荒波も乗り越えていこう
Let's ride over the rough waves.
“らしく”輝いていたい
I want to shine in my own way.
ねえ、君と会えたことが
Hey, because meeting you...
ねえ、宝物だから
...is my greatest treasure.
手を取り合い声かけ合って
Holding hands and calling out to each other...
地図など無い未知の世界で
...in an unknown world with no map...
まだまだ行こう！
...let's keep on going!
ridin' on dreams
急な風が僕らの
Even if a sudden gust of wind...
行く先乱そうとも
...tries to disrupt our path...
あの日誓ったんだ
...we made a promise that day.
覚悟は揺るがない
Our determination will not waver.
ちゃんとしなきゃ！って背中
Pushing ourselves to do our best...
明日への橋になる
...will become the bridge to tomorrow.
もっと大事にしなきゃね
We need to cherish this even more...
“あたりまえ”は無いから
...because nothing is taken for granted.
小さな船から始まるストーリー
A story that starts from a tiny boat...
どっから始めたらいいかもがいて
...struggling with where we should even begin...
少しずつね輪になって見つけた
...little by little, we formed a circle and found...
何にも代えられない夢だ
...this irreplaceable dream.
wow oh oh oh oh oh
未完成も愛して
Love even our incomplete selves.
wow oh oh oh oh oh
想いは一つだ
Our feelings are one.
wow oh oh oh oh oh
僅かな希望でも
Even if it's just a tiny glimmer of hope...
僕と君でずっと
...you and I, forever...
馬鹿にされても
...even if we are made fun of...
信じたい！
...I want to believe!
ねえ、ありがとうじゃ足りない
Hey, "thank you" is not enough.
ねえ、想いが溢れちゃうんだよ
Hey, my feelings are overflowing.
ずっと一緒だよ！
We'll be together forever!
ねえ、君がいたからだよ
Hey, it's because you were there.
ねえ、夢では終われぬ
Hey, we can't let this end as just a dream.
荒波も乗り越えていこう
Let's ride over the rough waves.
“らしく”輝いていたい
I want to shine in my own way.
ねえ、君と会えたことが
Hey, because meeting you...
ねえ、宝物だから
...is my greatest treasure.
手を取り合い声かけ合って
Holding hands and calling out to each other...
地図など無い未知の世界で
...in an unknown world with no map...
まだまだ行けるから！
...we can still keep going!
ひとりじゃない
You are not alone.
何度でも立ち上がってさ
We'll stand up again and again...
笑い合っていたい
...and we want to laugh together.
願いだってみんなで、さあ！
Let's make our wishes together, come on!
手を繋いで想像も超えて
Holding hands, going beyond our imagination...
まだまだ行こう！
...let's keep on going!
ridin' on dreams
wow oh oh…
Wow oh oh...
宝鐘海賊団
Houshou Pirates
撃ち抜いて
Shoot me!
あじまる
Ajimaru!
これが星街再演 サインぬい!!!!!!
This is the Hoshimachi rerun signed plushie!!!!!!
ローチケ当たったので、、、解散かも？
Since I won the Lawson ticket... maybe we disband?
声出せ!!
Make some noise!!
あしたは月曜日
Tomorrow is Monday.
マリン船長 400万人おめでとう
Congratulations Captain Marine on 4M subscribers!
ろく なな
Six... Seven...
F**kin ローソンチケット 落選
F**kin Lawson Ticket: Rejected
今日も天才
Genius again today!
声出ししていくぞ
Let's make some noise!
森カリオペ 推し!
Mori Calliope Fan!
あしたは月曜日
Tomorrow is Monday.
ロボ子さん
Robocosan
星街すいせい
Hoshimachi Suisei
アキ・ローゼンタール
Aki Rosenthal
宝鐘マリン
Houshou Marine
常闇トワ
Tokoyami Towa
ムーナ・ホシノヴァ
Moona Hoshinova
アーニャ・メルフィッサ
Anya Melfissa
カエラ・コヴァルスキア
Kaela Kovalskia
森カリオペ
Mori Calliope
オーロ・クロニー
Ouro Kronii
古石ビジュー
Koseki Bijou
ネリッサ・レイヴンクロフト
Nerissa Ravencroft
音乃瀬奏
Otonose Kanade
一条莉々華
Ichijou Ririka
儒烏風亭らでん
Juufuutei Raden
轟はじめ
Todoroki Hajime
hololive 7th fes. Ridin' on Dreams
ハーモニー重ねた言葉 届けて
Let the words of our layered harmony reach you
お互いらしく描いては
Drawing in our own ways,
「普通じゃない」と笑ってた
we laughed, saying, "It's not normal."
未来予想 あの日の続きを見よう
Let's look at the continuation of that day's future projection.
手と手つないで
Holding hands,
風も着こなして
carrying even the wind,
乗り越えた先に
beyond what we overcame,
進んでいくよ
we will move forward.
どんな時だってきっと
No matter when, surely,
一緒なら叶えていける
if we are together, we can make it come true.
La La La...
鳴りやまない 希望のベル ほら
Look, the endless bell of hope is ringing.
La La La...
聴こえてる (聴こえてる) 歌
The song is being heard (being heard).
ハーモニー重ねた言葉 鮮やかな日々の向こう
Words of layered harmony, beyond the vivid days,
いつも君と 踊るよストーリー
I'll always dance the story with you.
ハートに結んだ夢が
The dream tied to our hearts
空へ駆けていく
ascends to the sky.
煌めきに乗せて あなたへ届けて
Riding on the sparkle, reaching you,
メロディ どこまでも
melody, everywhere.
何気ないことも
Even casual things...
一人じゃないよって深呼吸
Take a deep breath, "You are not alone."
痛いけど楽しもう 魔法の言葉
It hurts, but let's enjoy, the magic words.
一息ついて
Take a breath,
振り返って
look back,
また君を知って
get to know you again.
その度に
Every time,
ちょっと勇気出して
gather a bit of courage,
明日へ踏み込んでいけ
step into tomorrow.
La La La...
積み積もる 道しるべは まだ
The piled up guideposts are still...
La La La...
覚えている 歌
A song I remember.
ハーモニー 手を伸ばしたら
Harmony, if we reach out our hands...
足跡に虹が架かる
a rainbow is cast over our footprints.
君とハレルヤ 打ち鳴らすステージ
A Hallelujah stage we play on with you.
ハーモニー 印した場所へ
Harmony, to the place we marked,
運ぶ約束を
carrying our promise...
輝きに乗せて
We ride on the radiance,
世界へ 響け
resounding to the world...
メロディー いつまでも
Melody, forever!
君と踏み出したあの一歩 あの瞬間が
That step I took with you, that very moment,
宝物だって胸を張るよ 今
I can proudly declare it as a treasure now.
歩いて 話して 繋いで 出逢ってゆくんだ
Walking, talking, connecting, meeting each other,
色褪せないままで
never fading away.
混ざり合う僕らの声 ほら
Our voices blend together, look!
聞こえてる？ 聞こえてる
Can you hear it? I can hear it.
歌おう！
Let's sing!
ハーモニー 重ねた音が 鮮やかな
Harmony, the sounds we layered together are vibrant,
日々の向こう ずっと君と 彩ってゆくストーリー
beyond the days, coloring our story with you forever.
ハーモニー 結んだ夢が 空へ 駆けてゆく
Harmony, our connected dreams soar into the sky,
きらめきに乗せて
riding on the sparkle...
あなたへ
To you,
世界へ
to the world,
響け
resound...
愛を
Love,
メロディー どこまでも
melody, everywhere!
parade parade parade！ 輝くんだよ
Parade, parade, parade! It's shining!
呼び合う声を合図に
With the voices calling each other as a signal.
parade parade parade！
Parade, parade, parade!
探しに行く
To search...
スタートは何度だって
the start, no matter how many times.
ただ独り言を綴った
I just spelled out my monologues,
ただ始まりたくて走った
I just ran because I wanted to start.
遠く暗がりに灯った
It lit up in the far darkness,
それは眩し過ぎた名前
that name was too dazzling,
それは優し過ぎる思い出 もっと
that memory was too gentle... more...
近づけと手を伸ばした
I reached out my hand, wanting to get closer,
思いがけず結び合った
unexpectedly, we were connected.
ほら 今 迷子 は “ 僕 等 ” に なった
Look, now the lost child has become 'Us'.
parade parade parade！ 輝くんだよ
Parade, parade, parade! It's shining!
悔しさも 愛しさも 連れておいで
Bring along the frustration and the love.
風、夢、羽 飛び立てるさ
The wind, the dream, the wings, we can take flight.
ささやかな祈りは 光
The small prayer is light,
終わりなき 兆し
an endless sign.
君を見つけたこと
That I found you,
胸を張れるよ
I can hold my head high.
ここから これから our bright parade parade！
From here, from now on, our bright parade, parade!
まだ頼りない予感を
Singing of the still unreliable premonition,
歌おう 恥ずかしくなんてないよ
there's nothing to be ashamed of.
誰も解けないイマジナリー
The imaginary that no one can solve,
いつかまた逢えるおまじない
a spell that we might meet again someday.
あの日ゼロに始まったストーリー
The story that started from zero that day.
数え切れない言の葉
Words that can't be counted,
数えるような想いじゃないさ
it's not a feeling like counting them.
ほら 今 “僕等” を 一つ と 呼ぼう
Look, let's call 'Us' as one now.
parade parade parade！ 美しいんだよ
Parade, parade, parade! It's beautiful!
許し合える刹那 夜はきらめく
The moment we can forgive each other, the night glitters.
雨、晴れ、カレイド
Rain, clear, kaleidoscope,
またとない空
the irreplaceable sky.
君と在ることさ
And here I am, right by your side
君と在ることなんだ
Cause there you are, standing by my side
ただいまを聞けば
When you're back and open that door
おかえりって叫ぶよ
You'll hear us saying, "welcome home"
当たり前じゃないか
Forever we'll be waiting
parade, parade, parade! 輝くんだよ
Parade, parade, parade! It's time to take the stage
暗がりを満たすのは 君だ 僕だ！
We're gonna shine right through the darkness, open up, share your light!
parade, parade, parade! 輝くんだよ
Parade, parade, parade! It's time to take the stage
悔しさも愛しさも 連れておいで
When disappointment gets in your way, love will shine, keeping you safe
風、夢、羽
Feel the wind and wishes
飛び立てるさ
Your wings will take you high
ささやかな祈りは光
These silent prayers will become our light
終わりなき兆し
Guiding us on an endless flight
君と飛び込んでゆく 素敵なスタートさ
Here I am ready to dive into a beautiful start with you
ここから これから our bright parade, parade!
Starting from here, starting right now, our bright parade, parade!
それじゃあ、次のステージへ、GO! スタートです！
Now then, let's GO to the next stage! Here we start!
風に吹かれて 誰も気づかぬよう
Blown by the wind, no one notices
区別がつかない モノクロの世界
Can't distinguish a monochrome world
ホロライブ 4th Fes! お前ら！ 最後のステージだ！
Hololive 4th Fes! Everyone! This is the final stage!
色を足しても 何も見えなくて
Even adding colors, I can't see anything
まるで私は 息を止めていた
It's as if I had been holding my breath
もういいよ
It's fine now
遠くても 叶えたい私は
Even if it's far away, I want to make it happen
こんな世界 想いも抱きしめていたいのに
I want to embrace my thoughts in this world, but...
夢のキャンバスに 居続ける意味は
On the canvas of dreams, the meaning of continuing...
この胸に輝いているストーリー
This story is shining in my heart
そして夜は その冷たさを
And at night, melting that coldness...
溶かして 手を伸ばした
I reached out my hand
もういいよ
It's fine now
遠くても 届けたい私は
Even if it's far away, I want to deliver it
受け止めてく 涙も抱きしめていたいのに
I want to embrace even my tears, but...
夢のキャンバスに 心込めるのは
On the canvas of dreams, what I put my heart into...
この空に 描きだしていくストーリー
Is a story being drawn in this sky
そして夜は その冷たさを
And at night, melting that coldness...
溶かして 手を伸ばした
I reached out my hand
もういいの
It's fine now
遠くても 叶えたい私の
Even if it's far away, I want to make it happen
こんな世界 想いも言葉で包んだ
Wrapping my feelings in words in this world
夢のキャンバスに 色を足していく
On the canvas of dreams, adding colors
この胸に 今輝いて
Shining now in my heart
強くなくてもいい 壊れかけてもいい
It's okay not to be strong, it's okay to be on the verge of breaking
この心は トワに羽ばたいて
This heart will forever soar
響くように 塗り替えていくpalette
Resonating, repainting the palette
強く
Strongly...
光に触れるたび願っているからね
I'll keep wishing every time I touch the light
La la la...
どれも哀を模したTRUE
Every one of them is a TRUE mimicking sorrow
はーい！みなさま！
Hi, everyone!
この靴は！私のお気に入り！
These shoes are my favorite!
今すぐグチャグチャにして、チュチュチュってしたいよ！
I want to make them messy right now, and go chu-chu-chu!
待っててね！
Wait for me!
りっさ、もう破裂しそう！
Rissa is about to burst!
抑えきれないの
I can't contain it
私のハートがクチュクチュしてる
My heart is going kushu-kushu
うるうるな瞳
Teary eyes
とがったくちびる
Pouted lips
いたずらな笑顔
A mischievous smile
いつも止まらないの
It never stops
私の頭ん中がクチュクチュクチュ保存
Inside my head, it's going kushu-kushu-kushu
あふれ出しちゃう
It's about to overflow
お隣の君までビンビン感じちゃう
I can feel it vibrating all the way to you next to me
恥ずかしがらないでよ 子猫ちゃん
Don't be shy, little kitten
隠れてないでよ 顔見せて保存
Don't hide, show me your face
片想い秒読み
Countdown for my unrequited love
脳内パーセンテージ 出力最大！
Brain percentage, maximum output!
見つけた！
Found you!
胸がキュンキュン 愛は止まらないの
My heart is throbbing, love won't stop
好き好き大好き marry me
I love you, love you, love you so much, marry me
私だけのお婿様保存
My very own groom
もう離さない ずっと
I'll never let you go, forever
教会で式を挙げましょう
Let's have a ceremony at the church
神様だって断れない
Even God can't say no
思い立ったので行っちゃおう
Since we've decided, let's go
ハネムーン お嫁ハニームーン
Honeymoon, as your bride, honeymoon
marry me
ただいま、ダーリン。
I'm home, darling.
お帰りなさいのチュウは？
Where's my welcome-home kiss?
さて、ご飯にしようか？ お風呂にしようか？
Now, would you like dinner? Or a bath?
それとも、わたし？
Or... me?
今日はこれから二人で楽しいショッピングデート！保存
Today we are going on a fun shopping date together!
ダーリン、もう準備できてる？
Darling, are you ready yet?
ダーリン、どこにいるの？
Darling, where are you?
もしかして、りさと隠れんぼしたいのかな？
Could it be you want to play hide-and-seek with Rissa?
テーブルの下？ クローゼットの中かな？
Under the table? Or in the closet?
よし、りさ本気出しちゃうぞ！
Alright, Rissa is going to get serious!
脳内パーセンテージ！
Brain percentage!
motto motto motto motto
甘い鼓動のリズム
The rhythm of a sweet heartbeat
赤い糸で二人繋がっているの保存
We are connected by the red string of fate
ハートがビンビン 降参、ベイビー
My heart is vibrating, I surrender, baby
見つけた！
Found you!
恋はもう誰にも止められないの
No one can stop this love anymore
好き好き大好き marry me
I love you, love you, love you so much, marry me
二人だけの愛の巣から
From our love nest just for the two of usSafe
もう逃がさない ずっと
I'll never let you escape, forever
永遠の愛を誓いましょう
Let's swear eternal love
神様サインを早く頂戴よ
God, please give us your sign quickly
我慢できない早く行っちゃおう
I can't wait, let's go quickly
ゴー・トゥ・ヘブン
Go to heaven
檻の中に囚われて
Trapped inside the cage
コール・イット・ラブ
Call it love
健やかなる時も 病める時も
In sickness and in health
命ある限り
For as long as we live
ラブラブチュウチュウすることを誓います！
I swear to be lovey-dovey and kiss you!
世界で一番...
More than anyone in the world...
...愛してるよ
...I love you
ベイビー、私を一人にしないで
Baby, don't leave me alone
あなたがいないとダメなの保存
I can't do this without you
寂しがり屋な私を
Since I get lonely easily
そばにいて ずっと
Stay by my side, forever
皆サマも！愛してるよ！
Everyone! I love you too!
胸がキュンキュン 愛は止まらないの
My heart is throbbing, love won't stop
好き好き大好き marry me
I love you, love you, love you so much, marry me
私だけのお婿様保存
My very own groom
もう離さない ずっと
I'll never let you go, forever
教会で式を挙げましょう
Let's have a ceremony at the church
神様だって断れない
Even God can't say no
思い立ったので行っちゃおう
Since we've decided, let's go
ハネムーン お嫁ハニームーン
Honeymoon, as your bride, honeymoon
marry me
ありがとう、ダーリン！
Thank you, darling!
チュッ！
Mwah!
あー！
Ah!
まりんのことめっちゃちゅき〜〜〜〜きぃ
I love Marine so much!
ナイナイナリナイナイナイ
Nothing, nothing, there's absolutely nothing!
ナイナイ船からナイナイ
Nothing, nothing, from the ship there is nothing!
背に腹代えられない
No choice but to make a desperate move...
前に Oh, what a...
before that, oh, what a...
円ドルポンドユーロ　マネーシュキシュキ
Yen, dollar, pound, euro, money, love it, love it!
ルピーアリアリドラムウォンドン
Rupee, Ariary, Dram, Won, Dong!
寄ってらっしゃい乗ったら
Come on over, if you get on board,
おいでな社長様
welcome, Mr. President!
お宝売りますわ
I will sell you treasures!
レッツ・ゴー・オークション！
Let's go auction!
どくろの旗？ No.1
A skull flag? No. 1!
オンボロパーカー？ No.2
A tattered hoodie? No. 2!
クリップに眼帯は？仕様済み No.3
A clip and an eyepatch? No. 3. Used!
How much? はい、100万円！
How much? Yes, 1 million yen!
からの？ はい、1億円！
And then? Yes, 100 million yen!
からの？ はい、1兆円！
And then? Yes, 1 trillion yen!
もう一声！
Just a bit more!
How much? はい、1000！
How much? Yes, 1,000!
からの？ はい、2000！
And then? Yes, 2,000!
からの？ はい、3000！
And then? Yes, 3,000!
ぶっ飛んで？ 5000兆！
Flying high? 5 quadrillion!
欲しい欲しいのマネーマネー
I want it, I want it, money, money!
助けて欲しいの社員社員
I want you to help me, employees, employees!
脱出よ！
Escape!
ぱれぱれぱれぱれぱれぱれぱれーど
Pa-re pa-re pa-re pa-re pa-re pa-re parade!
売り出せや お宝
Put the treasures up for sale!
トパトパトパトパ
Topa topa topa topa!
強引でもちゅき恋
Even if forced, love me!
賞味こり
Have you had enough?
なんちゃってね
Just kidding!
どろどろ欲望　かき回せ
Stir up the muddy desires!
メラメラ本能　満たされ...
Satisfy the burning instinct!
正気トキメキ　恋恋恋
Sanity, fluttering heart, love, love, love!
ぐるぐる世界が回されて
The world is spun round and round!
Get! スーパーチャーミングな
Get! Super charming...
音乃瀬奏
[Otonose Kanade]
一条莉々華
[Ichijou Ririka]
儒烏風亭らでん
[Juufuutei Raden]
轟はじめ
[Todoroki Hajime]
轟はじめ / 音乃瀬奏 / 一条莉々華 / 儒烏風亭らでん
[Todoroki Hajime / Otonose Kanade / Ichijou Ririka / Juufuutei Raden]
神様 この花びらを ある人は美しいと呟いた
God, someone whispered that this flower petal was beautiful.
この地球の横顔は 遠くで見ている君の世界では
In your world, watching from afar, the profile of this Earth...
現実を逆さまにして 無くしそうなものだけ 振り落とした
Turning reality upside down, I shook off only what I seemed about to lose.
手のひらで拾い上げようとしたら 指の隙間すり抜けて消えてった
When I tried to scoop it up in my palm, it slipped through my fingers and vanished.
形あるものだけが すべてじゃないけど
Tangible things aren't everything, but...
価値あるものが葛藤を知っても 走るよ
Even if valuable things learn of conflict, I will run!
この世界を変えることは きっとできないけど
Surely, I cannot change this world, but...
君の中の世界なら 変えられるはず
I should be able to change the world inside of you!
うつむいて咲いて実のって 晴れて
Bowing down, blooming, bearing fruit, clearing up...
なにひとつ隠せないから
Because I can't hide a single thing.
最後に君が笑ってくれれば
If you would just smile for me at the very end...
もうそれだけでいい
...that would be more than enough.
言葉を紡ぐ人 優しさを編む人
Those who spin words, those who weave kindness...
それぞれの正義を 分かってあげたい
I want to understand each of their versions of justice.
絡まった矛盾と辻褄合わせ
Entangled contradictions and rationalizations...
そんな切なさを抱え 今日を生きて
Carrying such sadness, we live today.
分け合った灯り 隣から隣
The light we shared, from neighbor to neighbor...
やがてひとつに 夜の帳へ
...eventually becomes one, into the veil of night.
息を吹き込んだ
We breathed life into it.
君とじゃなきゃ ダメなんだ
It has to be with you, or it's no good.
このまま寝てしまうには
To just fall asleep like this...
もったいないほど
...would be such a waste.
優しさにくるまった
Enwrapped in kindness,
夜だった
...was the night.
はっきり浮かび上がった 夢の輪郭
The clearly emerging outline of a dream...
それは確かに愛だった
...was surely love.
月が見守る航路 一瞬を立ち止めて
The route watched over by the moon, stopping for a moment...
きらめく星
...sparkling stars.
色や形 温度や響き
Colors, shapes, temperatures, and resonances...
それらすべて持ち寄ろう 僕らだけど
Let's bring them all together, though we are who we are.
きっと最後にあの音で繋がって
Surely, we will connect in the end with that sound.
この世界を変えることは きっとできないけど
Surely, I cannot change this world, but...
君の中の世界なら 変えられるはず
I should be able to change the world inside of you!
うつむいて咲いて実のって 晴れて
Bowing down, blooming, bearing fruit, clearing up...
なにひとつ隠せないから
Because I can't hide a single thing.
最後に君が笑ってくれれば
If you would just smile for me at the very end...
うれしいうれしいね！
We're so happy!
やった～！ありがとう！
Yay! Thank you!
じゃ、ちょっと自己紹介からさせていただきます！
Now then, let's start with our introductions!
カワイイ、ポジティブ...
Cute, positive...
ジーニアス！
Genius!
めっちゃ嬉しい！ホロライブDEV_IS ReGLOSSの一条莉々華だよ！こんりり〜！
I'm so happy! I'm Ichijou Ririka from Hololive DEV_IS ReGLOSS! Konriri~!
こんりり〜！
Konriri~!
や〜めっちゃ嬉しい！そして！
Wow, I'm so happy! And next!
ホロライブDEV_IS ReGLOSSの...儒烏風亭らでんです！
From DEV_IS ReGLOSS... I'm Juufuutei Raden!
なになになに？ええ〜？！
What was that? Eh?!
さっきまではあんなに...
You were so...
緊張してるって言ってたのに！
...saying you were nervous just a moment ago!
嘘つき！ / うるさい黙って！
Liar! / Shut up!
皆さん、楽しんでますか？！
Is everyone having fun?!
ペンライトも莉々華の色にしてくれてる！
You've also changed your penlights to Ririka's color!
ね！すごい！ありがとう！
Right! Amazing! Thank you!
はい、ということで...
Yes, and with that...
もうすでに何曲かみんなにお披露目できたと思うんですけど...
We've already performed a few songs for everyone...
今回ちょっとね、フェスのテーマとして「Ridin' on Dreams」ということで...
And this time, under the festival theme "Ridin' on Dreams"...
ステージとして皆さんの、お客さんのかけ橋の形がトロッコとして出てきました！
...as a stage, a bridge to all of you, the audience, appeared in the form of a cart!
動いたよ、ステージ！
The stage moved!
私たちも乗らせてもらったんですけど、本当に皆さんの笑顔が...
We also got to ride it, and seeing everyone's smiles...
嬉しそうな顔が見えました！
...and happy faces was amazing!
見えてたよ！めっちゃ見えてたよ、顔とか持ってるグッズとか！
We could see you! We could totally see your faces and the merch you were holding!
最高！
You guys are the best!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
せっかくMCを務めさせていただいたから、何かやりたいことあるんじゃないの？
Since we have this rare opportunity to MC, isn't there something you'd like to do?
社長、何かやりたい？
President, what do you want to do?
いや、もう、一番最初の全体曲の時から...
Well, since the very first group song...
なんか皆さんの掛け声とか、ペンライトとかが、もうぶわ〜って...
...everyone's cheers and penlights were just so overwhelming...
ぶわ〜って嬉しいくらい来て、ちょっとそれを、このMC中にもちょっとやりたいんですけど、いいですか？！
...it was so overwhelmingly happy, so I wanted to do that during this MC too, is that okay?!
いいですか？！
Is it okay?!
やった〜！
Yay!
え、じゃあ、莉々華は、ペンライトを使ってちょっと皆さんと交流したいです！いいですか皆さん、ペンライトの準備は？！
Well then, I want to use penlights to interact with everyone! Are you ready with your penlights?!
社長の色分かりよね？！
You know the President's color, right?!
ちょっと全部を、濃いピンク... 薄いピンクじゃないですよ！莉々華の濃いピンクにしてもらうてもいいですか？！
Could you turn them all to deep pink... Not light pink! Could you turn them to Ririka's deep pink?!
もうできてるよ！ / すごい！
They've already done it! / Amazing!
お花畑みたい！
It looks like a flower garden!
じゃあ次は、らでんのカラーである黄色にしてもらうてもいいですか？！
Then next, could you change them to Raden's color, yellow?!
黄色にしてくれるの？！
Will you change them to yellow?!
ありがとう〜！
Thank you!
じゃあ次は、莉々華が「ピンク」って言ったらピンク、「黄色」って言ったら黄色にしてね！
Then next, when I say "pink", change to pink, and when I say "yellow", change to yellow!
できるかな〜？
Can you do it?
行くよ！ピンク！
Here we go! Pink!
みんな変わってる！
Everyone is changing them!
すご！どんどん変わってる、どんどん変わってる！
Amazing! They keep changing, they keep changing!
ありがとう〜！
Thank you!
じゃあ、好きな色！
Now, your favorite color!
すごい！お花畑みたい！ありがとうございます、とっても嬉しいです！
Wow! It looks like a flower garden! Thank you so much, I'm so happy!
え、じゃあ、らでんは何やりたい？
So, what does Raden want to do?
え、らでんはもう分かってると思うけど...
Well, I think you already know...
らでんがちょっとこのDay 3のMCとして出たということは...
Since I'm appearing as the MC for Day 3...
今日何曜日だったかけな？
What day of the week was it today?
みんな知ってるよね。らでんが「明日は？」って言ったら皆さんも生まれてきて一番のでかい声で「月曜日！」って叫んでくださいね。いいですか？
Everyone knows, right? When I say "Tomorrow is?", please shout "Monday!" with the loudest voice of your life. Is that okay?
月曜日ですよ！行きますよ！
It's Monday! Here we go!
明日は？！
Tomorrow is?!
月曜日！
Monday!
最高！ありがとう！
Awesome! Thank you!
いやでも明日が月曜日でもね、そんな疲れも吹っ飛ぶくらい今日は最高のパフォーマンスをみんなで届けていきますので、皆さんまだまだ...
But even if tomorrow is Monday, we'll deliver our best performance today to blow away that exhaustion, so everyone, there's still more...
盛り上がっていきますよー！
Let's get fired up!
いくよー！
Here we go!
いいね！
Awesome!
もっといけるよね！
You can do even better, right?
まだまだいけるよね！
You've still got more in you, right?
いけるいける！
Oh yeah, you do!
はい！ということで、あのね、今回現地に来てくださっているみんなと...
All right! So, to everyone here at the venue today...
配信で見てくださっているみんなも！
...and everyone watching the stream as well!
そう、コメントも見えてますからね！
Yes, we can see your comments too!
見えてますので！
We sure can!
配信のみんなは、ハッシュタグ「#ホロライブFesエキスポ24D3」と...
For everyone streaming, please use the hashtag #hololiveFesEXPO24D3...
たくさんポストしてくれたら嬉しいです！
...and post lots of tweets! We'd love to see them!
嬉しい！
We really would!
そしてそして！楽しいお知らせがあるんですけど...
And also, we have an exciting announcement to make...
楽しいお知らせ？何？
An exciting announcement? What is it?
YouTubeとTikTokでご覧の方は、ここまでー！
For those watching on YouTube and TikTok, this is where the free stream ends!
えー！？
Aww!
寂しいよー！
That's so sad!
s:
Too sad!
はい！でもね、よかったら皆さん、まだまだ楽しいライブは続きますので...
Yes! But if you'd like, the fun live concert will still be continuing...
引き続き見てもらえると嬉しいです！
...so we'd love it if you keep watching!
はい、いっぱい声出して応援してね！
Yes, cheer for us with all your might!
応援してください！
Please cheer for us!
それではですね、ちょっと次の曲に入りたいと思いますので...
Now then, we're about to move on to the next song...
「せーの」って言ったら、みんなで今回のテーマである「Ridin' on Dreams」と叫んでもらえたら嬉しいです！いいですかー？
...so when I say "Ready, set...", we'd love it if everyone shouts out this year's theme, "Ridin' on Dreams"! Are you ready?
いいですかー？
Are you ready?
オーケー！
Okay!
それじゃあ行くよ！
Here we go!
せーの！
Ready, set...
Ridin' on Dreams!
引き続き楽しんでいってねー！
Keep having fun!
無料パートは終了いたしました！ご視聴ありがとうございました！
The sneak peek part of the show has ended. Thank you for watching.